Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
One who fa II In love cha nge the life!
Ma ke fa st hea rt bea t a nd ma ke slow brea thing!
Keep you a wa y from sleeping a nd
show you drea m In da y!
Tough you wha t Is life for living for someone!
Tough you how to step a long!
When you ha ve to pa ss your distence!
If you destiny Is Good
So you'll ha ve your love In just one shot!
Its Diffrent for me.
I got love three time!
1996 Very a wesome yea r!
I ha d know someone who ha d
motorola 's cell phone!
Me a nd Sa chin could a sk for the pepsi
In style!
April 1996 Piko.J. B a nd Me...
After Intermedia te.
We went europe by sponcering of a n compa ny!
Wha t a la s. There is every
gra ss a nd cow in switzerla nd!
Imported Cow.
Imported gra ss imported rock!
Will you brea k my score?
No sa chin its my ga me!
Its your fa ult.
Wha t I'll do In imported gra ss!
Where a re Imported Girls?
Look You a II ha ve to tha nks me!
You bought you chea per pa cka ge!
Therefore we could'nt see a ny girl!
Every where a re uncle!
Yes dude!
No girl sees me by evil eye yet!
Hey you Ja mmed bra in!
Hey Plea se Ca II me J. B!
Atlea st It ma y could ca II!
Now I ha ve to sa y lie tha t
I roa m there with girls!
But how would I know tha t
there wa s a cute roma ntic girl!
How much tha t a fter seeing Dil Wa le
Dulha nya Le ja yege she went europe!
In The hope of she could find ra j
like simren!
Why heroin could find hero In film.
A nd here the a II tour come to finish!
I'm unfurturna te now I'll ma rry with
my la nd lord a fter rea ch home!
Hosery price will works.
But fa ce must be like tome cruise!
Smile like sha rukh kha n...
a nd eyes like a mir kha n!
The voice like a mita bh!
And love like ra j!
Ra j is'nt rea I!
It could be.
Where a re you going!
To find ra j!
She going to ba throom!
I'm going to ma ke a wa ter!
There a re chicks In tra in!
He's very cute boy!
Where? There!
Boys pa ck up your lugga ge.
Bea cuse there's love a t next sta tion!
Give it to me
We should sa y hi to them
in style!
You should sa y. Me?
Yes you!
They a re my friends.
Ra j,J. B, a nd piko!
You hea red Ra j,
who is ra j in you?
He's ra j!
Ra j sa y hello to your sister!
Are dumb?
No sir. So wha t's the metter?
Sir I just wa s finding toilet!
Go upsta irs a nd left.
Tha nk you sir!
Pink is yours
Yes mine!
No dude I ha d chose her!
Are you choosing school bus sea ts!
Sa chin my best friend!
You ca me to know something?
Yes toilet is upsta irs!
Wha t?
You ca me to know tha t?
So If you ha ve much confidence
so go to yourself a nd a sk thier pa rents!
Pa rents!
I'm going to toilet!
How your pa rents could come?
From punja b!
You dude tha nks me!
Why?
Beca use I got the whole Informa tion!
Wha t a re you sa ying?
Tha t pink girl is... pinky!
No sweety.
She Pla ys ba sket ba II!
And tha t specs girl mona
Is english honor for a mritser uni!
Lea ve It!
Wha t Is your ma tter with na me?
Dont you wa nt Informa tion?
She'a findind Ra j!
Why?
I did'nt do a nything yet!
Tha t wa s the film Dil Wa le Dulha nya...
girls a re cra zy a bout the hero of
tha t. A nd she is more tha n them!
No dude I could'nt understa nd.
Which films? Sha hrukh kha n
They a re finding sha hrukh kha n?
No thier roma ntic hero!
The fa Iling in love in tra in
which ha ppend In film!
Tha t wa s rubbish...
Stupid!
Hey why you a re sleeping?
Tell me the story!
Whom of?
DDLJor else!
Dude tell me In short
Is there a ny emotions?
Tell you or not? Ok tell me!
You hea red?
Wha t?
Nothing!
He Is singing only tha t's does'nt mea n
He's ra j!
Whoever he Is...
he's cute enough!
If your pa pa sees.
Bea t you!
Come on.
The picture Is ta king!
You just go...
I'll ca II you!
I sa id where a re Girls?
There a re sitting furture
you just shuffle ca rds!
Hey Where Is Ba i?
Behind With uncle a unt!
Alwa ys pla ys ca rds!
Stop. Stop. Stop!
We a re a long In Tra in?
Were!
Tra in goes.
We missed!
I'm not silly.
You a re blind!
Tha t wa s here huh? Now It Is'nt
here still! Wha t's the mea ns of it?
But how could it possible?
Its a broa d!
How could tra in be missed?
Now?
Hey dont worry!
I'm with you I'll ta Ik to sta tion ma ster
He'll send your messa ge to your pa rents!
Tha t you a re sa ve a nd a II right
a nd meet you a t zurich!
I'm coming ba ck!
Wha t a na me my mom keept of mine!
Ra j!
Do you get a ny informa tion?
Yes next tra in Is 6 o clock In morining!
6 In a morning?
Mea ns 3 hours rema ins!
We a re In swetzerla nd just ma hi a nd his
ra j Cow a nd thier gra ss!
Should not sa y truth a t this situa tion!
The tra in will come tommorow evening
a t 6 o clock!
We should go by bus!
Bus?
If we could to rea ch a t time so?
No... we ha ve to hier a ca r!
Hey why a re you wa sting time? I ha ve
only one da y... tommorow Is my flight!
There a re much money with hero In film
a nd In rea I life you ha ve bike for ride!
My whole money spent by bike!
How much your rema ins?
I ha ve only ra ce money?
How ca n we ma na ge without money!
We'll why a re you worried?
You a re with me!
Nothing will ha ppend ba d!
Why. Wha t's the gua rentee?
Good ha ppend with good peoples!
I dont believe on it!
Wha t?
Tha t I'm Good!
No tha t every time you fa ce goodness!
OKey... ha ve you ever fa iled in ma ths?
No!
Your pocket money ever never been ca ncel?
Somebudy never ever ra g you In school?
No!
You got'nt every pimples?
You a re a n a lien!
No I'm just ma hi!
If could'nt woke up for exa me
so the pa per goes post pone!
If In school I dont like a ny girl
so her pa pa got tra nsfer!
If my pocket money got ca ncel
till when I got'nt my pocket money...
No one buy the pink sa ndle!
I'm just like tha t...
very lucky!
Plea se oke... you a re not much
lucky. You missed the tra in!
So wha t Is the ba d luck In It?
Ra j you a re very lucky.
Ma y be she Is very ruff girl... or dumb!
Your good will come to know when
we will die by sta rving!
How much fla vours
How it ta stes?
Ta stes mea ns?
We should try It!
Its your uncles Shop huh?
When seeing me he'll sa y how you ca me?
You a re so wea k...
come a nd ea t fa mous chocola te!
And I got it!
He'll be bea ten!
You sees wha t a killer I'm!
If you wish It'll be come true!
The kids do tha t...
no Am I a kid?
I do tha t.
Okey close your eyes!
Sha II we go?
Wha t kind of logic it is?
Wlsh logic. Never tells a fter wish!
Beca use wish will never complete.
Rea Ily!
Its mea n I wish nega tive so then tell
you so it will convert in positive?
How kind a logic its?
Wish Logic!
She ha s been tra p from tra in...
we'll rea ch a t zurich till morning!
As usua I I cra cked the killer idea!
Wha t ha ppend...
I think Petrol ha s been over!
Wha t?
Yes!
Wha t now?
You were telling a lot!
Come on...
we should find a ny clea n pla ce!
For wa iting for morning.
Do swea test ta Iking!
Till Morning? You gone ma d? Lets wa Ik
we'll find someone who ca n help us!
Hurry up!
Are'nt here a ny huma n being?
Switzerla nd's da ta tells here a re
1 ma n a nd 9 cows ra tio!
Ma y be you could see a cow a t corner
but I Promise, you ca nt find a ny ma n!
I'm sitting here...
you just go a nd find huma n being!
You know when I wa s kid I'd think tha t
The sta rs a re the bulb of God!
You a re kid yet!
When I wa s kid I wished to become
a strona uts...
I'll go streight In rocket.
A nd tells ra kesh sha rma...
tha t India looks very good
then whole world!
No Is'nt Stupid?
Its Sweet!
I wa nt to sa y something to you!
Ohhh... Fina Ily!
There a re discussing a bout my ma rria ge!
Dont know they found a boy!
He's from our community!
Ma hi... I wa nt to confess something!
Our bike petrol wa s'nt finished...
I ma de it!
Ma hi I rea Ily wa s'nt know tha t
you enga gment is being!
But Still petrol is rema ins...
Lets go... no!
Will you not a sk to me
why I did it?
Is'nt a wish if I tell you so
It will not complete!
I Rea Ily did'nt know your enga gment being
fix... but I wrote poem for you!
Look I knew tha t you will la ugh a t me...
Okey Lea ve it!
Plea se sing It...
Wont you la ught a t me!
I told you tha t Is Stupid!
No!
When I see you till when
dont know wha t ha ppend to me!
I ha ve never ever felt tha t.
Me too!
Its stra nge feeling huh?
Feeling sca red!
Tha t's it I knew tha t...
I'll found my ra j some da y!
Ohh... Why did'nt you tell me before...
I dra ged 4 km tha t bike!
Tha t's your mista ke. I told you If
you'll be with me you'll fa ce Goodness
Then I ha ve to be with you forever!
Forever!
You know wha t I wished?
Tha t you ma y miss your tra in!
You tells me...
Now It'll be miss In fa ct!
Pa ck your lugga ge... It wont
be outsta nd!
Listen, ha ve ma hi tells us
of here... Yes might be!
Where ha ve you been?
We were worried for you!
Dont know how could I missed the
tra in... I wa s so sca red!
I ha d'nt money... lf Ra j wa s'nt with
me... Pa pa Tha t's ra j
We were sca red...
you obliged a t us!
We ha d got the messa ge from
sta tion ma ster!
Son when you come to a mritser...
so must come to us!
Ma hi... Give him our a ddress!
Ok Kids... come in queue!
So now Will you ca II me?
No!
I'll come behind with you
to a mritser!
Will not you be la te?
Not a t a II!
So? So?
Hey wha t a re you showing style! Just tell me!
I know you a re killer...
Wha t ha ppend!
Tell me fa st!
Nothing ha ppend!
You a re so lucky...
Tell me wha t ha ppend?
Dont a sk to me?
First he wa s helping me...
Then wha t?
Will you kill us by supence?
He sent flowers for me,
Wa it! I'll show you,
Wha t ha ppen?
Lot ha ppen?
Everything?
Everthing, obviously,
If I will spend much time then won't
I get benefit?
She's in love with me a nd she
ima gines me in a groom's dress.
You people know, how much it ha ppens
with me.
First love then kiss then everything.
Tell us in deta ils.
I know,
I know, think wha tever you wa nt?
But I wa s just 18, should I tell
truth my friends in these ma tters.
I know, it ha ppens in tha t a ge,
I'm not gonna ma rry her, her ma rria ge
wa s a Iso fixed,
She must forgot me in a month.
Yea r 2002, pla ce Bomba y,
Sorry! Mumba i.
I've never seen rocking city like
this, live your life, don't interfere
a nyone, do wha t do you wa nt, even
neighbors don't know your na me.
Everyone is busy to ea rn money a nd
to chill.
I've been here from one yea r from
Dehli, I got a job in Microsoft.
I mea n money a nd fa me a nd
a nd Ra dhika.
My Ra dhika,
she ca me from Ra nchi.
Clothes in suitca se, some money in
pocket a nd bring some drea ms in eyes,
to become a filmsta r.
She just become a hot shot model in 1
yea r a nd my girl friend too,
excuse me, I mea n living girl friend,
without ma rria ge.
Ba be!
Coffee.
Wha t else you wa nt? Iove, a ffa irs,
tha t's wha t I a Irea dy ha ve.
We ha ve friendship, love, biology,
chemistry wha t you wa nt, everything.
Without a ny commitment, tha t's wha t
you ca II luck, wha t cha nge in a while.
Until living with Sa chin a s a pa ying
guest, I sa ved money
tha t I ca n a fford my own little
house.
Now not a nymore Sa chin, not his
nonsense a nd not his mess.
Just me a nd my bed will ta Ik mostly
how does it ha ppen if you will sleep
if you will sleep then...
Hey you! Decent people a re trying
to sleep here.
Wha t's your problem?
Ma 'a m problem is yours, a re you dea f?
Are you dea f?
Yes!
Very funny lower your volume,
Why? Beca use I a m your neighbour,
And it's your duty tha t you should
shout like huma n's volume.
A nd let me sleep,
7 o' clock in the morning, it's norma I
but I'm not norma I I mea n I work in
nights a nd sleeps on da y.
Hey! DJ open the door,
Wha t?
Sorry to disturb you, I ha d a little
request, if you don't mind.
I'm your neighbour.
I a m decent a nd belongs to a good
fa mily.
I got a good sa la ry, height 6 ft.
I went to Gym, I mea n if you lower
your volume then...
I would be very grea tful to you,
don't mind, sorry.
Oka y, I'm sorry I didn't know a bout
your working hours.
Sorry! I wa ke you up,
No! No problem.
It's not your mista ke,
Oka y bye.
Hello!
It's not my mista ke.
If she will a wa ke others then who
is gonna sleep?
And if ma n won't love his neighbour
then whom he would.
A fter four months we beca me two
bodies a nd one life,
two fla ts beca me one house forever.
I mea n not like tha t forever,
like for few moments,
forever like 18 months.
Coffee!
Tha nks sweety,
Toda y we both a re ha ppy from this
situa tion, who ha ve seen tomorrow.
It would must be ha ppen, Sa chin a nd
me work ha rd till three yea rs.
And toda y we prepa re such a rocking
ga ming softwa re.
Tha t we were ha ppy a nd our english
fa thers wa s a Iso ha ppy,
Welcome to the tea m, might.
See you in Sydney.
Dude! Sydney,
a nd there's white ba bes.
Dolla rs a nd ba bes.
Which kind of ma n you a re? We're
going to fiesta there not to ma rry.
Then sister in la w,
Who?
Ra dhika?
Wha t ha ppen to her?
Iove with you.
So she won't come sydney with you,
Why she would?
You're just a killer,
she lives with you.
Yes! But we joint our fla ts a nd
we didn't ma rried.
Ra j! You a re flirting a ga in.
Wha t do you mea n?
You know wha t I mea n.
It's in your pla n to drop her.
And you a in't told her a bout Sydney
yet.
I would, wha t's the tension?
Tension!
She will give you tension,
Rela x!
You don't know her, she's a modern
type girl.
And you think she lives with me
before ma rria ge.
She don't believe in old fa shion,
Wha t a re you sa ying?
Every girl believes in this,
They a re pla nning a bout ma rria ge
from the beginning,
First cool then stupid,
No! She's not tha t type of girl.
She is interested in her ca rrier more
tha n me, She wa nts to be a filmsta r,
wha t she will do in Austra lia?
You've gone ma d, just drink Ta quila,
She don't ca re,
Sorry ba by,
I know I should tell you before,
Even I didn't know tha t,
Yes!
We hea rd rumours,
but we got bingo.
They a re tra nsffering me a nd Sa chin
Sydney for five weeks,
I ha ve to increa se my work permit.
Everything just ha ppened in a moment,
We ha ve to ma rry in a court,
We don't ha ve time for selection,
we ha ve to do in five weeks,
tha t's why you were looking so
stress,
I a m with you, I'll ha ndle it a II.
We ha ve to get register in court,
a nd you ha ve to come for tha t.
I'll give house goods to Anusha,
fa rewell pa rty, clothes.
We a re going to Sydney.
But your ca rrier,
come on Ra j,
You know you a re very importa nt
tha n everything for me,
litttle bit of compromise, little bit
of sa crifice tha t you ca II ma rria ge.
If you a re with me,
I don't need a nything else.
Toda y is your most importa nt da y of
life, I a m so ha ppy.
You a re here,
Wha t else I need?
Wha t's going on with me, Why?
Wha t should I do?
Sa chin!
Wha t? Ha ve you gone ma d? Wha t
Mom ca n do? Everything.
Your mom ca n use your secret,
go a nd tell her tha t which kind of
woma n your Mom a re?
Wha t a re you sa ying?
My mom is very sweet.
You know tha t,
but she didn't
Go a nd tell her tha t your mother
finds a girl from Bha tinda,
Bha tinda?
Wha t ca res sa y a nything,
sorry, come to the point.
Mom word is very powerful,
tell your mother's na me
sister in la w out.
First you stop ca Iling her Bha bhi,
I wa s just getting ha bit of tha t.
Don't get ba d ha bits,
Mom, plea se forgive me.
Here he come,
one minute a unty.
You pee besides the tree,
Who you a re ta Iking to?
With our mother.
Mom wa s sa ying tha t Da d ha s a
surgery, they ca n'tjoin soon,
then we should proper reception in
december, we ca n get christma s
a nd new yea rs holida ys.
Yes!
December.
One second,
Mom wa nts to ta Ik to you,
Yes! Mom.
Promise Mom,
sorry Mom,
Yes! Yes! Yes!
No! No! No!
Every woma n ha ve a drea m tha t she
would ha ve few childrens,
Ba ntu a nd Chotu will bother her
forever,
but you go a nd tell her,
sorry! Not possible.
To ma ke Ba ntu a nd Chotu's fa ctory
wa s da ma ged in childhood,
Ha ve you gone ma d?
I'm not provoking you,
Just tell her,
she will never ma rry you,
Who is gonna touch da ma ge stuff?
Killer Idea.
I ca n't ever be a fa ther,
In childhood...
from cycle...
Why you didn't tell me before?
How ba be?
Even I ca n't ha ndle it.
You know, so ma ny tests,
still not possible.
Plea se give us a minute,
In just one minute my life will be
cha nge, In one minute I'll be free,
You know how much I love you,
I...
I a Iso ha ve a drea m like every girl,
A house
A loving husba nd in house,
two childs,
My childs,
I understa nd,
I need tha t house, a nd I need those
childrens from you
but with you,
We love ea ch other like our love
will never less for a nyone.
No ma tter it will be a n a dopt child.
Adopted child is more specia I.
And I get know toda y tha t how much
you love me.
You didn't hide truth from me,
tha nkyou.
A nd the best pa rt is, child's nose
will be like yours.
La ugh on my helpless condition.
8 August a t 3, you need 3 witnesses.
Anushka, Mrs. Shetty a nd Sa chin.
Sa chin do something ra ther I'll die.
Ba chelor Pa rty.
Think ba chelor pa rty,
Fiesta!
A show of lust.
Wha t a re you doing?
Pa cking.
Why?
I'm going to Anushka for few da ys.
Ra j!
You wa nt to sa y something to me,
No! Nothing, why?
Don't know from few da ys you're
beha ving stra ngley like you're not
Ra j, don't know who?
Like Sa chin type ma n.
I don't know wha t ha ppen to you,
This is the cha nce,
you forgot it.
Ra dhika! Actua Ily...
Am I doing something wrong?
I a m trying to ma ke everything
perfect.
Our ma rria ge,
our life.
But I fell tha t you're not ha ppy,
from me,
from us,
Is this necessa ry to cry?
A ny fight a ny discussion didn't
complete without this, tea rs come
a nd you're gone.
It's not like tha t.
I ha ve much stress, new job, new
responsibilties,
a nd you become so emotiona I
a re you ha ppy?
No!
I a m very ha ppy,
Dude! Wha t's the price of a nother
ticket of Sydney?
Do you remember on 8 a t 3,
If I'll forgot then how would I
remember our a nniversa ry.
Ten minutes left a t 3,
Ra j is a punctua I guy,
a Iwa ys 15 minutes la te,
His office ma tes a re sa ying tha t he's
gone Sydney this morning,
It's ha rd to ha ndle crying but it's
ea sy to brea k hea rt,
flight is fa r a wa y 15 hours la te from
India, but in India very fa r.
If someone lives here once,
he ca n't live a nywhere else.
Here's life, style of working here,
people of here, here's wea ther,
you ca n love every wea ther of here.
Love ha ppens in every wea ther.
Wha t so funny?
Nothing wha t ha ppen?
Nothing,
It's your ha bit to roa m in underwea r,
wher to go?
I'm hungry where we'll find food,
I ha ve ma ny idea s,
but nothing fa ncy.
Will it work?
It will run,
Why life isn't so simple?
Why people become phylosophica I to
wa tch sunrises a nd sunsets?
No! Seriously.
Life is like simple a nd complica ted
wha t you ma de,
then wha t's your simple pla n?
Wha t I does?
Job in da y a nd ta xi in night.
Now I know, business cool, then job
then ma rry with rich NRI, holida ys in
Ha wa i, shopping in Pa ris.
Wha t's the need of ma rria ge for these
things?
Beca use every girl wa nts to ma rry,
trust me.
Yes! But I'm not like every girl,
I know, you're cool, independent,
but in la st you'll come to ma rria ge,
drea ms of two childs a nd color scheme
of entire house in eyes.
I don't believe in ma rria ges,
There is no spa ce in my life, tha t
some husba nd come a nd fill it,
I don't sa y tha t every girl is wrong
but it's fine for me.
Ma rria ge?
No wa y.
Sha II we go,
meter is running.
It's more tha n 50 dolla rs,
Meter?
You turned on the meter?
Yes! You're pa ssenger a nd I a m driver
You wa nted to wa ste time, tha t's not
my problem, I get the point.
There will be more in store room.
It's not mine.
And a II this...
Look I got spa ghetti, a nd milk too.
I swea r I got milk, I don't know
whose trolly is this?
Wha t a re you doing here?
I work here.
You a re tota Ily sta r,
shopkeeper in da y, driver in night.
Ha ve you got other stuff?
Hello!
Yes! Sa chin.
I forgot,
Sorry! Sa chin!
Nothing, I ha d a big meeting, there's
a la unch of new ga me,
don't know how did I forgot,
which ga me, Helo 3
how do you know?
Come on dude, who doesn't know?
Nowa da ys wa Ilstreetjourna I is
ta Iking a bout whom?
Never a ny compa ny's stock didn't
become higher in less time.
Wha t a re you doin on Sa turda y night?
Why? You wa nt ta xi?
No! There's a la unch pa rty of ga me,
Will you come?
Do you ha ve nice dresses?
No! Shouldn't I come?
No! Come, come,
clothes no ma tters.
You brought a ta xi driver,
I a gree tha t she's hot but
you brought a ta xi driver.
She won't cha nge if you'll sa y
a ga in a nd a ga in.
Wha t ha ppen if she drive ta xi?
She's educa ted, intelligent,
My wa tchma n is a Iso intelligent,
I didn't bring him in the pa rty,
Why you a re over a cting?
Wouldn't I?
You were killer but now you're
beha ving like a punks,
work a II da y long then ta xi driver.
You brought a ta xi driver,
wha t ha ppens to you?
And you just sa id, she's not your
type, she's intelligent, educa ted.
You're getting tension for nothing,
she is a good friend of mine.
I ha ng with her,
Ha ng?
Dude! She's a girl,
When you sta rted ha nging with ba bes?
Ba bes a re for hunt not for
friendship,
Sa chin! Why don't you quit,
let me concentra te,
I didn't notice her one thing,
Ra j! Wha t? I'm ba rking since
ha If a n hour.
Didn't i disturbing you guys,
No! We were expecting you,
a ctua Ily we didn't ha ve a ny other
topic left to discuss.
Da ncde with me.
Is every girl like her a nd I didn't
noticed?
Or Ga ytri is like tha t, she's friend
bea utiful.
Little bit ma d, pretty too,
Intelligent, Sma rt
a nd I think
I'm fa Iling in love,
Look dude! You ha ven't a ttend
my phone from pa st two...
weeks, neither you come to
office nor I see your fa ce.
Now suddenly you a re
lea ving a long with ba g.
Dude I don't understa nd a nything.
Look dude! You don't ta ke tension.
Look I'm not getting a ny tension,
it's fight in understa nding.
I lea ving to sa y sorry
to Ma hi a n Ra dika.
Look brother try to
understa nd my position.
I'm too much old now a nd
my bra in works a bit slow.
A nd till now I ha ven't
ta ke liquor or a nything.
So let me a sk you once
more with feelings.
- Why?
- Beca use now I know how much pa inful it is.
Love somebody a nd he lea ve
to kick you on your ba ck.
So it's very pa inful.
So ba sica Ily you a re doing a II
this to bring ba ck Ga ya ta ri.
No dude! It's impossible
to Ga ya rti to be ba ck.
She don't love you.
Wha tever mista kes I did in my life
toda y I'm lea ving to correct them.
Don't know dude it
doesn't ma kes a ny sense.
Wha t you did since yea rs a go now
you a re lea ving to sort them out.
Stra nge dude.
Yes it's stra nge.
But it's right.
Look... It's simple, I broke hea rts a nd
now I know how much pa inful it is, boss.
When somebody's hea rt ha s broken
a nd somebody trea ts like Ra j.
And till the time I subside their
pa in my pa in won't be subside.
Tha t's why I think tha t a t lea st
my kind of swine ca n sa y sorry.
You'll be thra shed.
Tha t's isn't so simple dude. Ring
the bell a nd sa y hello sorry Ma 'a m.
I know but I ha ve to
do wha t I wa nt to do.
A nd rest upon their will.
- Tha t's me.
- Are you oka y?
Look if you wa nt to ba ng
somebody then ca II me.
- I'll ca II you
- And listen...
If they ha ve some hot sister then a t
lea st give me a n SMS instea d of phone.
Then I'll must do.
Yesterda y ha s gone, no control on it.
A nd tomorrow will be fine if
toda y I'll sort everything right.
- How much?
- 40 rupees.
I ca Iled a t her home in
lieu of credit ca rd compa ny.
So I come to know tha t
Ma heen is Mrs Ahlowa liya.
She ha s a little Ahlowa liya.
- Wha t do you wa nt?
- Hello Beta Is mother a t home?
Ama zing, Ha Iowa liya a nd Alowa liya.
Beta Is Mommy a t home?
Da ddy.
Why kid now a da y's don't listen?
No Goldie beta don't do like this.
- Yes.
- Hi.
Is Ma hi a t home? - She
ha s gone to her mother's
home, my sa a li Piya
is going to be ma rried.
- Who a re you?
- I'm Ra j.
Ma hi's friend.
I met Pa resecha fa mily in Switzerla nd.
Together we went on dera il trip.
Since yea rs I met her, how's she?
Be rea dy for it, Its
give pa in for few da ys.
Till the time you become
bla ck to yellow a nd then blue.
- Wha t?
- You a re mista king me with somebody else.
I rea Ily think there is
been some misundersta nding.
Are you swine Ra j Sha rma?
- Yes but swine.
- Myself Joginder Singh Ahlowa liya.
I'm Ma hi's Mr.
- Where is she?
- It doesn't ma ke a ny difference.
You a re a live a nd be ha ppy in it.
Sorry sir will I be a live?
A nd ha ve your whiskey ca Imly.
Don't worry, Lion never huntja cka I.
Sir I promise I don't
come here to gore.
You gore 12 yea rs a go a nd I'm suffering.
- You know a bout myself.
- Preety told me few yea rs a go.
- But I don't do such...
- If I ca n behold of so...
so I ba nged you right on the spot.
But now body knew
tha t where do you live.
- Sir Only I come to see Ma heen.
- Don't ta ke his na me.
Oka y Bha i Sa a b.
Aren't you thinking tha t still is
wa iting for you a nd dying in your love?
You correct your misundersta nding
otherwise I'm going to correct it right now.
No... sir... It ha s been corrected.
15 yea rs ha s been pa ssed.
First time I sa w her a t La wrence Roa d.
She ca me a long with Preety to ha ve Cha t.
Since tha t da y I fa II in love with her.
She ha dn't noticed me.
I wa s just without a ny rea son from fa ra wa y...
The problem is this toda y she's my wife.
But till toda y I love her from fa ra wa y.
I ca n't a ble to tell her. I'm
una ble to spea k butter words.
Which your kind of swine's knows.
You look week, no liver or no ba ckbone.
Don't know wha t she ha ve found in you.
Wha tever she sa w it's very hea vy on me.
Neither he believe on love nor
in roma nce. Neither she wa tch
pictures nor she listen songs.
She keeps everything hidden inside.
Only she do her duty.
My home is perfect. My wife is
perfect. My children is perfect.
Whenever I ta Ik a bout love, roma nce
a nd to spent time together...
She ca II upon to clea n the
shelf in the Kitchen by his mind.
Either I enga ge her in a speech.
Either I ta Ik to her.
Only I'm wa iting for tha t da y to see in her
eyes which she isn't a ble to see in my eyes.
- Now you a re Ra j.
- It seems he going to be drunk tonight.
I'm not Ra j you a re Ra j, you swine.
No sir Ra j from DDLJ.
Sa me chocola te hero.
Like wha t she wa s
looking her perfect loves.
- Sirjust give me five minutes.
- You will not a ble to get one second.
I'll kill you if you'll be
seen a round her vicinity.
You a Irea dy did too much mess,
no need to do a nything else.
I'm correcting your
mista kes since 12 yea rs.
If you come nea r by then
12 yea rs will be ta ken more.
No need to sa y sorry or a nything.
Sa rda r pra ctica Ily dropped me a t Delhi.
But I wa s killer, wa sn't
rea dy to lea ve such like tha t.
Oka y Ba dsha hoo here.
I fea red me a bit.
But for wha t I'm here, I'll do it.
And by the wa y I a Irea dy pa id
for three nights a nd four da ys.
So might is a s well.
Chocola te milksha ke sir.
- Ca n I ha ve a stra w.
- Yes sir.
I don't ha ve sta tus to ha ve
liquor, tha nks to Mr Ahlowa liya.
No he'll da nce. You people ha ve liquor.
Wedding pa rty.
- To Ka ra n a nd Proiya.
Priya.
Wife of Ba shera.
Come sir.
- Yes.
Such a good fa mily it is.
- Boy is good.
Look by yourself, there he is
in Green swea ter, Ka ra n Ba hel.
Solo son of Ba hel Electronics.
They ha ve two Bunga lows a nd hea rd tha t
they ha ve property in Golf-course a t Delhi.
Wow! Wha t is my concern
with his ma rket va lue.
I wa s just only thinking tha t there were
one or two idea s in DDLJ which ca n for me.
For him Cha mpa na ge from my side.
- Are you India n?
- Ha i go to Ba nk Koa k.
Oh tha nks pa I!
- Cheers.
- Cheers ca n't be done from fa ra wa y.
Come here a nd ha ve fun a long with us.
Use stra w if ca n't a ble
to stub out the butter.
Ma hi I'm coming.
Ma hi.
Hi Ra j.
Is he sa me one?
Wha t he is doing over here?
I don't know, he ha sn't
come with permission.
Ka ra n ca II him, isn't he?
- Yes.
- Is he from the groom side.
If it's such like tha t tha n don't
a Ilow Chotti to wed with Ka ra n.
If such people a re in Ka ra n's fa mily
then whole fa mily blood is rotten.
- Lea ve it Preety.
- How come I lea ve it like this?
This is the question of Chotti's
life. Abnorma I children will born.
I'll come ba ck a fter
getting some informa tion.
Don't do it Preety.
- From Pa tiya la.
- Yes sir.
- Is it Scotch?
- How ca n you da re tha t much?
There is something
different in Punja b a ir.
When you'll be ba nged then
a II of the a ir will be lost.
Right now I'm a voiding
you beca use of groom-side.
But if your knee or a nything
ha s been seen nea rby my
Ma hi... tha n a II the ceremony
will be ba ck to La mori.
Da ddyji's rifle is in the jeep.
A nd I know how to use it.
Ta ke ca re of yourself. Oka y ji.
Oka y ji, Tha nk you ji I'm
very plea sed to meet you.
How Punja bi's love is spiting
out a nd ha s been seen a II over.
- Off course.
- No...
Not a t a II.
Son my eyes ha s been mista ken.
You a re the sa me guy who
missed tra in with Ma hi.
Enough I got a nother sla p.
Son tha t da y I ca n't sa y
tha nk you to you properly.
You helped us a lot.
Son I'm Khushi's fa ther.
I'm sa ying it from
the depth of my hea rt.
Our fa mily will never
forget your kindness.
Consider this home like yours.
- Tha nk you sir.
If you need a nything don't
hesita te to a sk for it.
Long live son.
Hi Ma hi.
Hello.
- I wa nt to sa y...
- Food ha s been served.
Plea se help yourself.
It's buffet India n,
Chinese a nd Continenta I.
- Are you listening?
- Excuse me.
Meet him he's Ra j.
He's such a nice ma n.
- I don't wa nt to wea r it.
- Do a ct like this Beta.
How bea utiful my son is looking.
Both of them ha ve to
be Bla ck ca t security.
They a re wa sting their life in Punja b.
Ka ra n where is drums a nd other stuff.
Err! Wha t a re you
doing? Guests will lea ve.
Allow me to pla y otherwise
I'll compla int o mother.
If you sa y to Mom then I'll ta Ik to Da d.
Da ddy fea r a lot out of Mom.
I'm not a fra id of a nything.
Wha t a re you doing?
I'm looking my ga mes.
Wha t ga mes do you ha ve?
- I ha ve Bio-shock...
Ca rja ck 4 a nd Ha Io 3.
Ha Io 3.
- Yes.
I a Iso wa nt to pla y.
Sorry I only a Ilow my friends to pla y.
Then we ha ve a friendship.
My na me is Dumpy.
And my na me is Ra j.
And wha t ga me do you ha ve in excha nge?
In excha nge.
Nothing a nd tha t Goldie took, owl.
Alright if you don't ha ve video ga me
then some other ga me will be fine.
But a II the boa rds a re a t home.
Now I think something else.
How tha t ca n be possible
tha t groom is da ncing?
Won't you do it.
No Ka ra n I'm sorry.
Lea ve it Ka ra n, Didi don't ha ve
interest in tha t kind of stuff.
Mom Goldie ha ve trouble in his
stoma ch he's ha ving pa in in his
stoma ch a nd he's crying. He's
in the wa shroom a nd doing No. 2.
Good Lord I'll be ba ckjust now.
If you'll see Bha nda ri
then ha ng him with you.
Sa me night she left for Ita ly.
On lea ve.
I didn't ha ve a ny other wa y.
So I a Iso hit Ita ly.
After her.
Ra j Sha rma.
Tha nk god you recognize me.
How ca n I forget you? But
wha t you a re doing over here?
Do you come to sa y hello?
I become fa mous, do you
come ha ve a n a utogra ph?
No Ra dhika I'm very ha ppy.
I'm rea Ily proud of you.
So tha n... Oka y...
You come to ta ke benefit of my success.
I come here to sa y sorry to you.
Ra dhika I know I didn't
do right with you.
I do the lea st ba d move.
Me.
- Sa y.
I wa nt to listen.
I'm a low, ba d, cowa rd
a nd greedy kind of person.
Look how much it's ea sy to spea k truth.
Ra dhika wha tever I did wa s wrong.
And toda y I come to sa y sorry a bout it.
Ma 'a m Hea d Hunters phone ha s
come PA a rra ngement is being done.
How much a re despera te
you a re for my forgiveness?
Very much.
Are you rea dy to do a nything?
You a re hired.
You come on work from toda y's evening.
Ha ve you need forgiveness?
So you will ha ve to work ha rd.
It ca n't be ea sy to a chieve.
From toda y he's my PA.
Show him the work.
- Ra dhika how come this is...
- La st time...
My na me is Shriya.
Shiriya Ra thod.
Yes Ma 'a m.
Congra tula te for new job, Ra j.
Assista nt to Miss Shriya Ra thod.
My a la rm clock wa sn't work...
- You a ren't permitted to spea k.
Rule no 1 Persona I
a ssista nt a ren't huma n.
They a ren't a Ilow to
think, understa nd a nd spea k.
Only they ha ve to follow the orders.
Cha nge your cloths I
ha ve pa rty a t my home.
And you'll be wa iter.
Go a nd serve the guests outside.
Come on hurry up.
You will not be seen
a fter 15 minute over here.
Tomorrow I ha ve a n meeting in
Rome you go to the dry clea ner.
And yes, a double shot Ca pea ichino
with Skim milk no suga r.
I ca n a fter it before
the meeting is over.
Only from Bra lize.
This isn't be so ea sy.
Nor she's going to dissolve soon.
So Ma 'a m wha t cruelty you
do I'll fa ce it open hea rtily.
Still it's on tha t one.
Wha t a re you doing? Are you blind?
Do it properly.
Bring out the na il polish.
Rea Ily you a re too much
despera te for my forgiveness.
Mea ns wha tever worse beha ve
I do to you. You gona ba re it.
Ra dhika I'm sorry.
I'm rea Ily sorry.
They wa y I trea ted you I
ha dn't ha ve to do it like tha t.
I a Irea dy ha d to told you the truth.
Tha t I'm not rea dy for ma rria ge.
Honestly I wa s too much a fra id.
Tha t's why I ra n a wa y instea d
of beha ving in ma turity.
Ma y be I ga ve you more pa in.
You don't ha ve a nything missing Ra dhika.
I wa s disa ble.
Tha t's why I'm a sha med of my mista ke.
Bull shit.
I wa s missing.
I wa s tha t kind of girl 'fa st' beca use I
wa s living a long with you before ma rria ge.
Boys don't ma rry with my kind of girl.
Don't introduce my kind
of girl with mother.
My kind of girl don't
you da re to deny it.
You know tha t's the truth.
You'll never come to know.
Tha t how I felt tha t da y.
I fell like some kind for chea p tra sh.
Which ha s been thrown a wa y a fter use.
Beca use if I ca n sta y with
you so I ca n sta y with a nybody.
Right.
Right it isn't like this.
- I know...
- You don't know nothing.
How would you know?
Wa sn't you be there?
When I wa s wa iting for
you in bridle dress.
Wa s you there?
No.
It wa s my wedding da y for God Sa ke.
The bea utiful da y of my life
a nd you destroyed it forever.
I never sa w you kind
of person till toda y.
You a re the worst kind of
huma n being ever possible.
You don't know nothing.
Now you a re a fra id of tha t
somebody else will come out like me.
A nd a ga in brea ks your hea rt.
So you brea k everybody before
he's going to brea k you.
So you got the cha nce to put
down the world on to your knees.
So you a re ta king benefit out of it.
Don't do such like tha t.
Plea se only ma n ca n suffer in it.
Sta ys a Ione.
And tha t is you, Ra dhika.
And I'm not a Ione.
I'm on top.
And the person who is on top
a s you put it, is powerful.
This is my life a nd it's perfect.
People love to die to live
the life of Shiriya Ra thod.
Soft drinks compa nies offer... a long with
Shriya, like Sriya a nd spent a da y with Shiriya.
You ca n't be cha nged
by cha nging your na me.
Just shut up.
Wha t you ha ve to do you did it.
A nd you ca n't do a nything to remove it.
Go from here Ra j.
This ga me is over.
Lea ve from here a nd
don't ever come ba ck.
I'll never forgive you.
Sa chin wa s right tha t isn't so ea sy.
Come a nd sa y sorry Ma 'a m.
Why she forgive me?
I ca n't even forgive myself.
It ha s to be considered tha t wha t I ha ve done
with tha t girl if somebody did it with me tha n...
Nobody hea rt me tha t much till toda y.
Tha t much you did.
And nobody did tha t much ha rd
work to correct his fa ult.
I'm tired.
To ha te you is my ha bit now.
Apa rt of my life.
Wherever I ca n go, on shootings,
shows, ma keup, recordings loca tions.
I a Iwa ys sta y outside the
office of tha t registra r.
I'm still hooked up in tha t 8th August.
If toda y I ha ven't forgive you tha t ma y
be I'll be hook a t the sa me pla ce forever.
So you forgive me.
Yes, I forgive you.
Actua Ily I ha ve to sa y tha nk you.
Nor you lea ve me or neither I
be a tha t much big sta r in a nger.
Turn into Shriya from Ra dhika.
And you'll not come on knees to
sa y forgive me... forgive me...
So Shriya ca n't become Ra dhika.
Sometimes a bit shock is being needed.
To recognize our self.
This is a different ma tter
tha t you give high shock.
But I forgive you.
I'll not go such like this.
I'm very plea sed to hea r this.
Me too.
Sha II I sa y something, whoever
you like he must be a killer.
I know.
Ta ke ca re of yourself.
I don't believe tha t wha t
I wa nt to do, I did it.
Now I feel good inside.
And toda y first time I feel
tha t Ra j Sha rma isn't a ba d ma n.
- How a re you?
- I'm fine how a re you?
You a re a killer to wha t
you wa nt to do you did it.
Let's go somebody is wa iting for you.
Who?
- Err! Move.
Your sister a nd my dove.
Anna.
Dude do you remember tha t Russia n?
Good looking a nd excellent to pla y.
- Will you ha ve a try?
- Wha t else.
All the life you stea I
a nd pla y my ga mes.
Now it's my turn.
- I'm bla st.
You don't know how much
I da re to write you.
Ra j I broke your hea rt
but I'm ha ving pa in.
I left you but why I'm missing you?
It's ha rd to brea th to
tell you my hea rt feelings.
I ta ke you a pa rt of my da y a nd I write you don't
know you rea d it or throw them a fter rea ding.
A nd while la ughing tha t
how much fool she is.
Toda y I'm there... Where you were a n
yea r a go a nd tha t isn't a nice pla ce.
I'm sorry. I love you Ra j.
Tha t old times love long
la sting forever kind of love.
Ga ya tri tell him tha t ta xi is mine.
You a re still driving the ta xi.
Is there a ny problem?
- No I don't ha ve a ny problem.
By the wa y you wrote me
those letters I just sa w them.
Just sa w?
I wa s writing them from six months.
From six months.
And you noticed now.
I mea n wha t is wrong with you.
No I wa s a broa d.
For six months.
Why?
Are you on lea ve?
I wa s gone ma d while crying over here
a nd you were chilling on some bea ch.
Drinking Pena -Cola da 's.
Don't mess with me.
Do you know you ha ve a n
hockey stick Jelendha rwa la.
A nd you know Ta ekwondo.
You ha ve to inform me tha t
I'm going to be missing.
I know, don't know
why I didn't ca II you.
Now I remember you dumped me.
You left me.
You, I told you a nd you left.
Wha t ha ppen beca use of my words?
Don't you ha ve your bra in.
Wha t is this logic?
I'm a girl I ha ve full
right to cha nge my decision.
And my job is to tra ck tha t cha nging decision.
When your decision cha nge into my fa vor.
Tha t wha t I wa s doing.
Wha t?
Do you know I sa id
to you tha t I'll wa it.
I ca n wa it on the sta ge I'm,
I'll wa it for whole life.
Why don't we a re stopping
here Rome is there
Just Shut up.
This is importa nt.
And you get out.
Isn't it funny you a re
ta Iking inside in front of him.
And outside nothing...
- Just shut up.
I'm trying to think.
Do you know how much ha rd it is?
I don't ha ve ha bit to a ccept my mista ke.
Sha II I help?
I lea rn this a ccept a nything else.
Tha t how to sa y sorry.
I know wha t you'll sa y tha t
you love me a s much I love you.
You'll sa y tha t I cha nge you.
And you'll a sk tha t ca n we
sta rt over this rela tion a ga in.
Do ha ve the sa me love
in your hea rt for me?
The one forever.
If I'll sa y yes then wha t will you sa y?
Do you get your a nswer?
Still now you love me tha t much.
You see it's sa me.
Loving you is like loving myself.
We both a re stupid.
We both think where a re we.
But we ma ke mista kes...
We a ren't perfect.
We both a re just like
sa me like tops curvy.
Tha t's why we a re ma de for ea ch other.
Tha t's why I love you so much.
A such a killer philosopher sa ys,
tha t yesterda y ha s gone, no control
on it a nd tomorrow will be cure
when toda y I do something right.
Hello I sa id tha t...
Wha t a killer I'm?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org